You must be
Song Shiya.
You are Pei Song.
Hello.
Let me declare
that coming to this blind date
was not my intention.
That's fine.
I'm only here
because my family pushed me.
Let's get straight to the point.
Let's sign a
marriage agreement for three years.
Once the three years are up,
we will get a divorce.
During this time,
you don't have to do anything.
You just need to
play the role of a good wife in front of the public
and my family.
Of course,
during the agreement,
I will try my best to meet
any requests you have.
But just one thing.
I don't have much time to spend with you.
Because I am at home
for no more than thirty days a year.
You are Pei Song.
Let me state clearly first,
coming to this blind date
is not my real intention.
Whatever the reason,
since you're here,
just give it a try.
We can see if the elders' recommendation
is accurate.
How about it?
What's wrong?
What do you want to say?
Nothing.
I just feel
you are somewhat different
from what people say.
So you are Song Shiya.
We
still have plenty of time
to get to know each other.
Well,
can we first
sign an agreement?
Agreement?
Let's sign
a three-year marriage agreement.
What agreement?
Although I know
it doesn't follow the rules,
I am really not ready
for marriage.
What I mean is,
we just met.
After getting married,
can we live as friends
for a while first?
If it works out,
we'll take it further.
If it doesn't work out,
it's better to separate.
You mean
we divorce when the time is up?
For example,
a one-year limit.
Three years.
What?
You must stay with me for three years.
If the time is up
and you feel it doesn't work out,
we can divorce then.
I will respect your wishes.
Shiya.
This time,
I won't let go again.
Copy the code he wrote
onto this USB drive,
and you're good to go.
When are you planning to get married and move in?
In the next couple of days.
We won't be having a wedding.
Keep in touch.
You sleep in the master bedroom from now on,
and I'll take the guest room.
Thank you.
I saw on your profile
that this is your favorite flower.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Have you been to all these places?
I went to all of them with you.
No.
But
if you want to go,
we can find time to go together.
Have you read all these books too?
I read all of these specifically
to understand you better.
I've read most of them.
I didn't expect we'd have
so much in common.
What's wrong, Shiya?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Are you okay?
I'll do it.
Don't do it.
Are you hurt?
What's wrong?
I...
The smoke got in my eyes.
Let me take a look.
I'll
get the door.
I'll be right there after I change.
Grandpa.
Okay.
Grandpa,
why are you suddenly here?
It's so late.
What?
Can't I come see my granddaughter-in-law?
I was planning
to take her to see you tomorrow
and have a meal together.
What do you mean?
Am I not welcome here?
No.
I mean,
it's very late now
and we were about to rest.
I'm staying here today
and not leaving.
What's with the 'ah'?
Don't you have a guest room?
Grandpa.
Well.
When I lived alone,
you could come anytime.
But now,
Shiya is at home.
Isn't it a bit
inappropriate?
Why is it inappropriate?
You sleep in your room,
and I sleep in mine.
How is that inappropriate?
Alright.
Don't worry.
Whatever noises you make at night,
I won't hear a thing.
It won't affect my rest.
Grandpa.
Well.
Okay.
Grandpa,
stay here tonight.
I'll go prepare the guest room.
No.
As for this,
don't worry about it.
Let Song do it.
Sit down.
You.
Just stay with Grandpa
and chat.
Why haven't you gone yet?
Hurry up.
This brat.
Okay.
He wouldn't even let me stay.
Is he shy?
No,
of course not.
Pei Song.
Don't misunderstand.
I'll sleep on the floor.
You'll just have to make do for tonight.
After Grandpa leaves,
I'll sleep in the guest room.